Prakhar Awasthi

https://gitlab.com/Prakhar_Awsthi

Profile

Software Developer with 3+ year of experience having skills in Data Analytics, Machine learning algorithms and Android studio.

Skills

Python Data Visualization (Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Scikit Learn) (PowerBI, Excel) **Database** Mobile (SQL- MySQL, SQL Server) (Android Studio)

Projects

2022 - present **Authyn** HR/Employee Management System • Employee Recommender System using deep learning. 06/2021 - present Kiniko B2B Sales App • Dashboard using EDA and Analytics in PowerBI. 03/2022 - 10/2022 **OEMS** MPNRC Exam Management • OCR using OpenCV to fetch data from different student marksheets. • Mobile app for taking student attendance and tracking answer sheets. **UC - Health App** 10/2021 - 02/2022 Hospital Management System • Patient appointment and lab report generator. • Bill generator and payment integration. 07/2020 - 10/2021 **UC - BMW App** Bio Medical Waste Management • Android app for tracking bio medical waste generated in hospitals. • Integration with bluetooth and wired weighing machine. 06/2020 - 01/2021 **mAccord App** Company Management Software

- Android app for mobile and tabs.
- Face Recognition using deep learning in TensorFlow for attendance.
- Location tracking, timesheet management, HR operations.

Professional Experience

06/2020 – present Senior Software Engineer

Upside Cloud Technologies

09/2019 – 02/2020 **System Engineer Trainee**

Infosys

Education

2015 – 2019 Bachelor of Engineering

Pune Sinhgad College of Engineering , University of Pune

CGPA: 8.4

2014 Intermediate

Kanpur Dr. Virendra Swaroop Education Center

89.6%

2012 High School

Kanpur Dr. Virendra Swaroop Education Center

CGPA: 10

Interests

Stock Option Trading

• Guitar

• Boxing